{"componentChunkName":"component---src-pages-all-answers-js","path":"/all-answers/","result":{"data":{"allGoogleSheetAnswersRow":{"edges":[{"node":{"id":"51c6b6cb-cc30-5206-8268-f210b9254285","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"biden","candidateInfo":"Senator from Vermont (or however you want to say it)","candidateName":"Joe Biden","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Joe Biden long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Joe Biden short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"dcb59d35-83ab-5621-b65d-9c41b8f1ab34","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"sanders","candidateInfo":"Former Vice President","candidateName":"Bernie Sanders","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Bernie Sanders long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Bernie Sanders short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"52af65a6-ca3a-5554-9786-7fb2438fe51b","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"warren","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Elizabeth Warren","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Elizabeth Warren long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Elizabeth Warren short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"c71f0d83-4f80-55bc-b956-6bc70dedf2f8","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"bloomberg","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Michael Bloomberg","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Michael Bloomberg long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Michael Bloomberg short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"409c105d-6803-5eb9-933e-ecdf50a3f175","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"steyer","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Tom Steyer","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Tom Steyer long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Tom Steyer short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"a98e08d7-6b17-5d87-9fdf-77cac4956c5e","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"klobuchar","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Amy Klobuchar","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Amy Klobuchar long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Amy Klobuchar short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"4cece7c9-fdce-5bed-83f4-521a179e56ce","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"buttigieg","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Pete Buttigieg","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Pete Buttigieg long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Pete Buttigieg short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"8e2dc68a-b013-53ee-a427-1a9d72589a2b","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"yang","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Andrew Yang","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Andrew Yang long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Andrew Yang short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"20c77de2-3e72-5b57-92a7-20e381c3b035","background":"Background on state health","candidateId":"bennet","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Michael Bennet","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Michael Bennet long answer about state-health","questionSlug":"state-health","questionText":"If your federal health care agenda does not advance, would you support state efforts to create single-payer systems and would you grant approval for federal dollars to help fund those systems?","shortAnswer":"Michael Bennet short answer about state-health"}},{"node":{"id":"d5e07c26-873e-547d-86af-ba00235a2a1d","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"biden","candidateInfo":"Senator from Vermont (or however you want to say it)","candidateName":"Joe Biden","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Joe Biden long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Joe Biden short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"2816edba-324c-51c2-aff1-67bc3c4e9615","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"sanders","candidateInfo":"Former Vice President","candidateName":"Bernie Sanders","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Bernie Sanders long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Bernie Sanders short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"6abb5c5f-ab9f-5078-bd77-77b4c08cc2b8","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"warren","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Elizabeth Warren","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Elizabeth Warren long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Elizabeth Warren short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"0ee34f94-4dfb-5426-88ce-178895664658","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"bloomberg","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Michael Bloomberg","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Michael Bloomberg long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Michael Bloomberg short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"85a3bc36-63d3-52e3-8c6d-a01523ff8ea0","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"steyer","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Tom Steyer","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Tom Steyer long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Tom Steyer short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"741c0090-0206-5500-9334-fe26485dd982","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"klobuchar","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Amy Klobuchar","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Amy Klobuchar long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Amy Klobuchar short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"e17d8033-6da5-5680-8401-c3d93479e944","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"buttigieg","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Pete Buttigieg","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Pete Buttigieg long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Pete Buttigieg short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"164281c1-dd92-551a-8398-389a1b8f8766","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"yang","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Andrew Yang","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Andrew Yang long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Andrew Yang short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"4f7fecea-9b92-52be-9ee1-0142106881f6","background":"In a bid to reduce prescription drug costs, Colorado state health officials are developing what would be one of the nation’s first drug importation programs. But the state can’t do it alone. Under a 2003 law authorizing the practice, federal approval is required to import drugs from abroad -- and to date no state has ever received it. President Donald Trump supports doing do, but even if the state received the go-ahead by the end of 2020, the next administration would still play a role in such a program’s implementation. One major hurdle that could demand the next president’s attention: Canadian officials have concerns about the idea, and could unilaterally block drug exports to the U.S. before such a program can get off the ground.","candidateId":"bennet","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Michael Bennet","category":"Health care\n","longAnswer":"Michael Bennet long answer about drug-import\n","questionSlug":"drug-import\n","questionText":"Do you support giving states the ability to import prescription drugs from other countries?","shortAnswer":"Michael Bennet short answer about drug-import\n"}},{"node":{"id":"accb2353-d9e7-5ccb-8c73-be5253d10faa","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"biden","candidateInfo":"Senator from Vermont (or however you want to say it)","candidateName":"Joe Biden","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Joe Biden long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Joe Biden short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"72559e61-ef91-5e0d-a88c-7b9a1f7c1bae","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"sanders","candidateInfo":"Former Vice President","candidateName":"Bernie Sanders","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Bernie Sanders long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Bernie Sanders short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"599d2b48-3ce7-5b24-bf56-e9aa4a23850e","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"warren","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Elizabeth Warren","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Elizabeth Warren long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Elizabeth Warren short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"129f7991-fe30-5888-9512-e4637039354f","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"bloomberg","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Michael Bloomberg","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Michael Bloomberg long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Michael Bloomberg short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"e3c433ec-7f0e-54fd-847e-14f25924e4ab","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"steyer","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Tom Steyer","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Tom Steyer long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Tom Steyer short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"dd0956c6-0266-5beb-8476-6396430f93dd","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"klobuchar","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Amy Klobuchar","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Amy Klobuchar long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Amy Klobuchar short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"6b52e3e8-c579-5a2c-99d3-4d5bf6f56975","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"buttigieg","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Pete Buttigieg","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Pete Buttigieg long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Pete Buttigieg short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"c6d1fa35-e065-5499-a547-67210f807c42","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"yang","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Andrew Yang","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Andrew Yang long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Andrew Yang short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}},{"node":{"id":"24c53429-37be-5976-a35c-a2a78cbc4b18","background":"Background on legal marijuana\n","candidateId":"bennet","candidateInfo":null,"candidateName":"Michael Bennet","category":"Marijuana","longAnswer":"Michael Bennet long answer about cannabis-legal\n","questionSlug":"cannabis-legal\n","questionText":"Do you support the legalization of marijuana at the federal level?","shortAnswer":"Michael Bennet short answer about cannabis-legal\n"}}]}},"pageContext":{}}}